portwallpaper.com 2008-09-16

# Download center, Lisisoft software ,free software, download software

**TERMS OF USE**   
Permission is granted to display, copy, distribute and download the materials on this Site for personal, non-commercial use provided you do not modify the materials and retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the materials. You may not, without Panload's permission, "mirror" any material contained on this Site on any other server. This permission terminates automatically if you breach any of these terms or conditions. These Terms of Use constitute a legal agreement between you and Panload. By using this Site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms, do not use this Site.  

**PANLOAD PRIVACY PRACTICES**  
This statement discloses the privacy practices for the Panload Web site. Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Panload Corporation at: info@Panload.com.

Personal Information  
We may ask you for certain personal information for purposes such as, but not limited to, newsletter subscription or product registration. If you choose to give us such information, you can be assured that we do not share or sell our customers' personal information to anyone.

If you have provided us your personal information so that we may contact you, and later decide that you do not wish to be contacted by Panload, we will respect your wishes.

Web Tracking Information  
We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics and then we discard it.

Information Security and Quality  
We intend to protect the quality and integrity of your personally identifiable information. We have implemented appropriate technical and managerial procedures to maintain information that is accurate, current and complete. We will make a sincere effort to respond to your requests to correct personal information inaccuracies in a timely manner.

Business Relationship  
The Panload site contains links to other Web sites. Panload is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Cookies  
There are various technologies, including one called "cookies", which can be used to provide you with tailored information from a Web site. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system.

If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices, you can contact us at: Contact Information.
